{
    "id": "290af61d7ad340c681a99c000c19900f",
    "title": "Simple present / Present continuous: Grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "55e6b1ab226a4eac9e14af6d0a9948b1",
            "title": "Simple Present Or Present Continuous Tense",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Every morning, my dad ………….. for a walk in the park.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "go",
                        "goes",
                        "is going"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………. some old friends this week.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "visit",
                        "am visiting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Don’t make a noise. The baby ......................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "sleeps",
                        "sleeping",
                        "is sleeping"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The kettle …………………. Shall I make tea?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "boils",
                        "is boiling"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………. this wine very much.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "like",
                        "am liking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Don’t forget to take your umbrella. It ..........................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "rains",
                        "is raining"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She doesn’t like to be disturbed if she .........................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "works",
                        "is working"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "My brother ………………. in Paris at the moment.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "works",
                        "is working"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He …………………. his grandparents about twice a year.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "visit",
                        "visits",
                        "is visiting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………….. what he says.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "not believe",
                        "don't believe",
                        "am not believing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}